Martin Klefas-Stennett - CV (Continued

Martin Klefas-Stennett

Phone: 07985 706256 | Email: martin.klefas@hotmail.com | Open to Relocation & Remote Work

GitHub: https://martinklefas.github.io/ | https://www.linkedin.com/in/martin-klefas-stennett/

Skills Machine Learning Python Computer Vision C++ Fortran90 SQL Srategic Thinking Problem Solving Relationship Building

Education

- 2023 AiCore Machine Learning Bootcamp
- **2006-2008** Ph.D. Computational Chemistry, U. of Manchester (Published, not completed)
- 2005-2006 M.Sc. Computational Science
- & Engineering, U. of Manchester (Merit)

Languages

Basic Polish, French & German

Hobbies

Photography enthusiast, World Travels, Triathlon

Personal Profile

After more than 13 years of experience in sales and business development, creating and using automation and analysis tools to enhance productivity, I retrained in machine learning. I am eager to apply my new skills to a career in machine learning, combining my background in account management, automation & analytics, relationship building, and strategy with a passion for cutting-edge technology.

Experience

Machine Learning & Data Science:

Artificial Intelligence Engineer - OpenPatho Al Healthcare (June 2023 Onwards)
As part of an agile and dynamic team, I contributed to the creation of an advanced

detection framework for pre-cancerous growths in colo-rectal tissues, now advancing towards full-scale clinical trials. My role encompasses:

- Designing and developing a robust, scalable AI model framework for accurate detection of pre-cancerous growths in colo-rectal sample tissues.
 - Collaborating with healthcare specialists to ensure precise and reliable classifications.
 - Used a number of foundational models from META, OpenAI, HuggingFace and others
 - Enhancing open-source projects with bug fixes and improvements where necessary.
- Leading the development of a continuous improvement and deployment workflow to streamline operations.
- Coordinating resource acquisition and allocation to facilitate project milestones.

This role not only emphasizes my technical expertise but also highlights my ability to work collaboratively and lead in a high-stakes environment.

AiCore Machine Learning Bootcamp (Q1 2023)

I undertook several lecture courses and applied the knowledge to vocationallyoriented mini-projects. As a result, I successfully:

- Developed a working implementation of part of the Facebook Marketplace Recommendation Algorithm (github)
 - o Python, FastAPI, PyTorch, Docker, AWS
- Developed a a simple CNN to classify hand gestures in a live webcam feed for playing a game of rock-paper-scissors (github)
 - o Python, OpenCV, TensorFlow, NumPy
- Developed a system that extracts data from five disparate data sources, creates a new master record, and extracts metrics from the new system (github)
 - o Python, Pandas, PostgreSQL

Continued overleaf

Business Development Roles:

Insight UK Ltd - Public Sector Business Development Manager (2014 - Present)
I streamlined the role by automating labor-intensive repetitive tasks using VB.net,
MSSQL and SQLLite, which allowed me to focus on delivering greater value to the
business. As a result, I successfully:

- Secured and developed relationships with vendors specific to the Insight UK Public Sector business, focusing on HP, Cisco, and Dell as key suppliers.
- Guided the campaign and sales activities of partners and managers by providing and amending sales data reports to suit their needs.
- Worked on major Public Sector opportunities, engaging with C-Level contacts and securing multi-million pound tender wins for Insight.
- Developed and implemented automated workflows for various areas of the business, streamlining processes and improving overall efficiency on an informal basis.

Direct Sales Roles:

Insight UK Ltd - Internal Account Manager (Education) (2013 - 2014)

- · Designed simple automation steps to maximise productivity
- Responsible for recommending appropriate options to meet challenges faced by Network Managers & senior staff.
- Analysed sales & marketing data to allow me to exceeded all targets for gross profit.

ANSYS UK Ltd. - Academic Account Manager (2009 - 2012)

- Sold engineering simulation software suite directly into the UK academic market.
- Understood strategic goals of departments and universities to position sales.

Other Sales Roles:

NCC Group Ltd. (2012) & Egencia - Internal Account Manager (2012)

- Generated new business leads for an external account manager.
- Exceeded all targets for growth and meeting bookings.

ANSYS UK Ltd. - Internal Sales Rep. (Team leader) (2008 - 2009)

- Promoted the value of ANSYS Software and consultancy services
- Generated leads for a sales team of 12-14 external account managers.
- Automated essential marketing tasks, leading to increased reach and reduced marketing expenditure while optimizing campaign performance.